examcompass.com 2017-06-26

# Privacy Policy

This Policy was last modified on January 5, 2016.

Please read this Privacy Policy ("Policy") carefully before using http://www.examcompass.com ("the Site") operated by ExamCompass ("Us", "We", or "Our"). This Policy is intended to provide the users of the Site ("User", "You", "Subscriber", "Visitor", or collectively "Users", "Subscribers", "Visitors") with information on what kind of data is collected by the Site about its Users and how the collected data is handled. By accessing and using the Site, You agree to be bound by this Policy. Capitalized terms are defined in this Policy.

### Personal information collected on the Site

The personal information collected on the Site is restricted to names and email addresses, and this information is gathered only through contact and newsletter subscription forms available on the Site. Personal information collected through contact form enables Us to answer comments and questions submitted by Users. We use email addresses collected through newsletter subscription form to tell Subscribers about discounts on educational products.

The Site adheres to anti-spam policies, i.e. We do not send unsolicited emails to Users who do not request Us to do so by subscribing to the newsletter. We also do not send Subscribers messages that are unrelated to the general topic of the Site (computer education / IT certification training). We do not share any personal information submitted by Users / Subscribers with any third parties, however We may disclose this data if required by law.

### Non-personally identifiable information collected on the Site

**Log files**  
Like in the case of many other sites, We collect data which is stored in the server log files. The information inside the log files includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date / time stamp, referring / exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Site, track User movement around the Site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies**  
The Site uses various types of cookies. A cookie is usually a small piece of data sent from a webiste and stored as a text file on a user's personal computer or mobile device. When the user browses the same website in the future, the data stored in the cookie can be retrieved by the website to notify the website of the user's previous activity. Cookies are used by websites and servers to provide many of the basic online services. Websites, for example, may use the information stored in cookies to keep track of the items stored in a virtual shopping cart or remember personal preferences set by the user for the website during their next visit. A more detailed explanation of what cookies are and how to control or delete them can be found at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

**First-party cookies**  
First-party cookies are cookies that are set by the Site directly.

**Google Analytics**  
The Site uses Google Analytics by Google. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to report on visitor interactions. These cookies are used to store non-personally identifiable information, such as browser type, operating system, the date and time of a visit, where visitors came from, visited pages, the time spent viewing site, return visits to the site, and other anonymous metrics. This data is transmitted to Google and then used to compile statistical reports on User activity for the Site. We collect this non-personally identifiable information to better understand how Visitors use the Site, and to help manage and maintain the Site.  
If You wish to opt-out of Analytics, please visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and follow the on-page instructions.

**Joomla! CMS**  
The Site uses Joomla! Content Management System (CMS), and first-party cookies are set by Joomla! to store basic data on User interactions with the Site. Apart from the core Joomla! CMS, the Site also uses Joomla! extensions installed on the core CMS that enhance its functionality and these extensions will also generate cookies. We deem cookies set by Joomla! as strictly necessary to the proper working of the Site. If You choose to disable cookies, a detailed guide on how to control cookies for all the main browser types can be found at the [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) website.

**Third-party cookies**

**Google AdSense**  
The Site displays AdSense ads by Google. Google's use of the [DoubleClick cookie](http://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=2839090) enables it and its partners to serve ads to Users of the Site based on their previous visits to the Site and/or other sites on the Internet. You can opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Google's [ads preference manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/).

**Social media sharing widgets and third-party vendors**  
Third-party vendors may use cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons to collect data about Users visiting the Site. For example, when You share a web page using a social media sharing button on the Site, the party that has created the button will record that You have done this.

Please note that the Site has no access to or control over the cookies that are used by third-parties. Please consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party vendors for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This Policy does not apply to and We cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or websites.

You can generally opt-out of cookies from third-party advertisers and ad networks by visiting their Sites (if the advertiser or ad network offers this capability). It is also possible to opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), or [Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) opt-out web pages.

If You wish to disable cookies, you may do so through individual Internet browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1), or at the browsers' respective websites.

### Acquisition or changes in ownership

In the event that the the Site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, Your information would be considered part of those assets and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

This Policy was last modified on January 5, 2016.

Please read this Privacy Policy ("Policy") carefully before using http://www.examcompass.com ("the Site") operated by ExamCompass ("Us", "We", or "Our"). This Policy is intended to provide the users of the Site ("User", "You", "Subscriber", "Visitor", or collectively "Users", "Subscribers", "Visitors") with information on what kind of data is collected by the Site about its Users and how the collected data is handled. By accessing and using the Site, You agree to be bound by this Policy. Capitalized terms are defined in this Policy.

### Personal information collected on the Site

The personal information collected on the Site is restricted to names and email addresses, and this information is gathered only through contact and newsletter subscription forms available on the Site. Personal information collected through contact form enables Us to answer comments and questions submitted by Users. We use email addresses collected through newsletter subscription form to tell Subscribers about discounts on educational products.

The Site adheres to anti-spam policies, i.e. We do not send unsolicited emails to Users who do not request Us to do so by subscribing to the newsletter. We also do not send Subscribers messages that are unrelated to the general topic of the Site (computer education / IT certification training). We do not share any personal information submitted by Users / Subscribers with any third parties, however We may disclose this data if required by law.

### Non-personally identifiable information collected on the Site

**Log files**  
Like in the case of many other sites, We collect data which is stored in the server log files. The information inside the log files includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date / time stamp, referring / exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Site, track User movement around the Site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies**  
The Site uses various types of cookies. A cookie is usually a small piece of data sent from a webiste and stored as a text file on a user's personal computer or mobile device. When the user browses the same website in the future, the data stored in the cookie can be retrieved by the website to notify the website of the user's previous activity. Cookies are used by websites and servers to provide many of the basic online services. Websites, for example, may use the information stored in cookies to keep track of the items stored in a virtual shopping cart or remember personal preferences set by the user for the website during their next visit. A more detailed explanation of what cookies are and how to control or delete them can be found at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

**First-party cookies**  
First-party cookies are cookies that are set by the Site directly.

**Google Analytics**  
The Site uses Google Analytics by Google. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to report on visitor interactions. These cookies are used to store non-personally identifiable information, such as browser type, operating system, the date and time of a visit, where visitors came from, visited pages, the time spent viewing site, return visits to the site, and other anonymous metrics. This data is transmitted to Google and then used to compile statistical reports on User activity for the Site. We collect this non-personally identifiable information to better understand how Visitors use the Site, and to help manage and maintain the Site.  
If You wish to opt-out of Analytics, please visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and follow the on-page instructions.

**Joomla! CMS**  
The Site uses Joomla! Content Management System (CMS), and first-party cookies are set by Joomla! to store basic data on User interactions with the Site. Apart from the core Joomla! CMS, the Site also uses Joomla! extensions installed on the core CMS that enhance its functionality and these extensions will also generate cookies. We deem cookies set by Joomla! as strictly necessary to the proper working of the Site. If You choose to disable cookies, a detailed guide on how to control cookies for all the main browser types can be found at the [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) website.

**Third-party cookies**

**Google AdSense**  
The Site displays AdSense ads by Google. Google's use of the [DoubleClick cookie](http://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=2839090) enables it and its partners to serve ads to Users of the Site based on their previous visits to the Site and/or other sites on the Internet. You can opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Google's [ads preference manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/).

**Social media sharing widgets and third-party vendors**  
Third-party vendors may use cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons to collect data about Users visiting the Site. For example, when You share a web page using a social media sharing button on the Site, the party that has created the button will record that You have done this.

Please note that the Site has no access to or control over the cookies that are used by third-parties. Please consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party vendors for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This Policy does not apply to and We cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or websites.

You can generally opt-out of cookies from third-party advertisers and ad networks by visiting their Sites (if the advertiser or ad network offers this capability). It is also possible to opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), or [Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) opt-out web pages.

If You wish to disable cookies, you may do so through individual Internet browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1), or at the browsers' respective websites.

### Acquisition or changes in ownership

In the event that the the Site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, Your information would be considered part of those assets and may be part of those assets that are transferred.
